[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What are you hearing that might be remotely factual?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, there is obviously a lot of confusion about the information coming out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "He will die for the cause if need be and he's going to create as much bloodshed as it takes to try and stay in power, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "That does seem to be the case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "How much longer can you hold on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Already here in Libya, it's a completely different case, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "That makes this a very dangerous situation, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "I mean this is sort of potential Armageddon for Libya if any of this actually happens, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "Certainly is.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "Can you hear me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "I'm sorry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "Commissioner Kelly, this is pretty worrying, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "Well, it certainly is cause for concern for those of us here in New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kelly"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Would you say that the risk now to cities like New York and America is greater than it was in 2001, for example?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Well, I think the risk has been pretty consistent.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2001"], "LOCATION": ["New York", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "Do you think the national homeland security threat level should be raised?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "No, not for this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Is that not an increased threat that perhaps they will try something to reinforce that point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "It's possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "This gentleman broke into your house a few -- a couple of weeks ago?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "I think gentleman would be an overstatement.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "How would you describe him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Well, we have described him as mentally ill and he is currently in a lockdown of a psychiatric unit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "Were you there at the time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "No, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "What was your feeling when you heard about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "Well, my feeling was just simply to react logically.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 265, "question": "Evasive, I imagine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 266, "answer": "You know --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Do you get a lot of crank people turning up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "TONE: Well, as I'm sure you've come to realize with your own celebrity, you get all kinds of fans and all kinds of incidents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "You were there stalking me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Not stalking you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "When would you call it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I don't really think of it like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What are the negatives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "I don't -- I don't really leap to the negatives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "15 or 17?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Sixteen, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "What was the advice they gave you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "They really talked to me about keeping my feet on the ground and really enjoying every moment and really staying in my gratitude and grace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "ORGAN: When you have the kind of incident you've had to deal with recently, is any part of you wish you could turn back on the anonymity cloak that you once had?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "-- kind of stop being crossed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PDT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Was it you that made it the most paused moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I'm happy to claim all credit for this, seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "TONE: You were in there with the remote?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "How do you feel -- seriously, you're the most paused woman in the history of movies, that moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Are you proud of that moment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I think that the film as a whole, because it's been like, 18, 19 years -- I think the film has actually held up for people and has created a sort of passage for a sexual identification for people, and a way for people to speak about the way that they feel about themselves, the way they want to communicate about their sexuality.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Because you kind of admired the way she went about her work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "How I became like her was not in a sexual sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 411, "question": "Were you horrified?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 412, "answer": "I think more I was just so shocked and I was embarrassed not to be able to process it alone with him than I was so horrified.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "Have you talked to him recently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "I -- I don't think I've spoken directly to him lately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "ORGAN: Do you think it is karma?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "I think part of it genuinely is karma.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Not going to let me in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Who knows what you're going to do in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "Who do you fancy this year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "The wonderful thing about this year is there are so many great people in all the categories.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", ":", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "RB", ":", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Which way are you going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "TONE: You know, I think both those films and \"The Fighter\" - these are kind of films that just -- all of them were just so astonishing that I had to watch all of them more than one time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "If you could only watch one again the rest of your life, what would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "If could I only watch one film for the rest of my life, it's probably not a film from this year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bertolucci"]}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What would be the movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "I'm a huge Bertolucci fan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Are you going to be on the carpet on Sunday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "Well, I have to get in there.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "Do you like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "That's how you get in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Billion of people around the world going, what's she wearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "You know, I don't really think about it like that anymore, because this has been my life for so long.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is there a vacancy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "I don't really to have get back to you about the men in my life, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Where would you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "I would say all of the above.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Not true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Their just over-anxious about me being alone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "You don't look like you've had any scalpel stuff there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "TONE: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Can you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Actually, mine is natural.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "Would you ever go under the knife?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I hope not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "How are they getting on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "They're really good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 629, "question": "ORGAN: How are you getting on being a single mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 630, "answer": "Well, you know, when I had this bright idea that I should go ahead and pursue this course of action, I was a younger person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Do you need a guy to help you out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "You're trolling here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "What the hell was I wearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "Look how cute we are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Lovely to be here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Diana", "Charles"]}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "And I'm delighted you've joined our team, because this is the wedding of the century, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "This is going to be the biggest royal story, yes, since Diana and Charles.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "And looking at pictures of William and Kate with their first proper royal engagement up in Wales, what did you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "This was crunch time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kate"], "LOCATION": ["William", "Wales"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Earth"]}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "She seems a normal girl, doesn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "She is so down to Earth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["ABC"]}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Have you been invited to the wedding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "I'm going to be covering the wedding for you and for ABC.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110224pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 712, "question": "Don't we?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 713, "answer": "I think you're very right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]